All right.
>> All right. I'll see you boys later.
>> Show us. What have you got there?
>> Little cigar courtesy of Sundell. Thank
you.
>> I think you deserve that.
>> Thank you. Yeah. No, it's uh it's
surreal.
>> Surreal.
>> Uh all my boys from uh they they were
back in Sydney watching the game and uh
I just FaceTime FaceTime them real
quick. coming over and they're all uh
they're all pumped.
>> Have you I know it's been a stressful
focus on the significance of what this
means. Right now you're sitting here
with a cigar. You have won a Super Bowl.
That must be the best buddy feeling in
the world.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it is. It really is.
Um,
I'm so lucky to uh to get to experience
this just as a as a human to get to
experience this type of uh feeling is is
uh not many people get it. So, I'm super
grateful.
>> Yeah, I mean uh this week was was no
different to uh to any other week in the
in the in the year. So, you know, I
always uh always want to give my my
defense the best uh the best field
position. And uh it was cool, you know,
uh hitting it inside the tent a few
times and getting the boys around me. It
was uh it was special.
>> Oh, yeah. He's uh he's elite. the um
he I mean he's the the amount of um the
attention that goes into the detail with
him. It's it's really cool to see and it
it pays off and he he's cool to be
around. He he's elite. He's got that
that mentality and it's it's really cool
to be to uh to share this experience
with him.
>> MVP.
>> Did he get robbed? Uh, I mean, we need
multiple MVPs cuz K9, he he went off.
He's he's incredible.
>> Wasn't just tonight though with Jason,
right? Like all season setting the new
record for points in the year. He's been
doing this all year long.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He He's a robot. He'll
he'll make them all and he'll he'll go
get the record and then hit a kickoff
and then go lay a guy out on uh on on
kickoff. So, he's um he's special.
>> How are you going to celebrate? How am I
going to celebrate? Uh I mean I I'll
just sit I mean if we just spent three
days in the locker room and just hung
out, I'd be happy to do that. We don't
need to do anything. It's just being
around these guys and uh getting to
share this experience is is incredible.
You know, we're going to be 60 years old
doing reunions and stuff and I'm so
happy that I get to get to do that with
this group.
>> And you mentioned something I saw in an
interview about
and the like. Tell me about that. So,
you came to have a party.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. I I just ultimately I
just want some chicks. Uh, it's not
chicks. I just want some chips with some
chicken salt. That's really That's what
I'm missing. That's what I'm missing.
>> Chicken salt.
>> Oh, chicken salt. I mean, I try and I
try and put the guys on here, but they
don't they don't get it. They don't get
it.
>> Australians in the Super Bowl is an
exclusive list. What What does this mean
to you being
>> It means a lot. I mean, I'm I keep
saying it, but I'm just I'm just pumped
that I get to share a ring with with
this team because
it couldn't be a better group of guys.
There's uh there's no egos. There's it's
just, you know, brothers in the locker
room every day. We get to go to practice
together. We get to hang out in the
locker room together, go to meetings
together, and uh you know, we're so
lucky that uh that we're that we're this
close and get to share a ring together.
for your fans back in Australia was
celebrating your punts. It was such a
big story. Twitter was all over your
punt.
What do you have to say to your fans
back in Australia?
>> Yeah, I mean, love you guys. Uh I'm glad
that you guys can appreciate some punts.
Sometimes it's uh it's a position that
that gets overlooked, but uh you know,
>> shout out to the people on Twitter and
everything that are uh showing love.
When a game's close, there wasn't a
third point. Does every guard count? Is
that what is that your mindset when
you're
>> Yeah, definitely. Um, I mean, I just
want to have a positive impact on the
team. I want to do do everything I can
to uh put our put our guys in the best
position possible.
Yeah, I mean, uh, Jay Harbaugh obviously
spoke to us on the sideline. He he gave
us a heads up saying, "Hey, they're
probably going to do this." And, you
know, gave me a chance to hit some in
the net at a at a faster get off. Um, so
going out there, I I knew that it was
going to have to be quick
because, you know, if if they get a
block there, it's it can change the
game. So I knew that uh once I saw the
returner come up, once I saw the the gem
has come in and I knew it was an 11man
box and, you know, we only have 10 guys
protecting me, I knew that I needed to
operate at really fast level. Um, and
you know, I caught it and stole snaps a
perfect ball and I was able to get it
off quickly because of that.
Um, yeah. I mean,
>> yeah, there's uh I mean there's a lot I
I'll be here for for a while as you can
see. Um, you know, it's just a lot of
punting punting cues and mentality
mentality cues for me to uh bring into
the game. And there's a lot going on in
the game and sometimes your your mind
can, you know, it's it's hard to
remember this novel that I have on my
wrist. So, I write it on my wrist and it
and it really helps me.
>> Oh, yeah. Stoley, he's um he's the best.
He's the best in the world. He uh he
some of the snaps today just felt like a
felt like a video game. They came out so
perfectly. It's pretty impressive to be
able to be upside down throwing a ball
to an area this big and on field goal
matching laces. Um he's uh he's
incredible and we're we're really
grateful for Stalie.
>> Do a couple more. What was the reaction
on the sideline after made that tackle?
>> Um I mean we were already celebrating
him because he he set the record in the
Super Bowl, of course. Um he's been
setting records all year, so it was only
right for him to do that. And for him to
then go down and and light the dude up.
Uh, I mean, I was just I was just
laughing because it was like, of course,
of course you of course you light him up
and and do that. Uh, yeah.
>> Anything else, guys?
>> Last one.
>> Australia.
>> Uh, I mean, I'm pumped. I I'm glad that,
you know, the uh the NFL is going to
Australia. It would be a dream come true
for me to play in Australia. So
hopefully next time, you know, the
Seahawks get to go there. But I know
that I know that it'll sell out. I know
that the fan base for uh for American
football back home is huge. So um those
guys are lucky that they get to play
there.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I go I go back quite a lot.
Um you know, I spend a good chunk of my
off season back home and uh you know,
play some tennis and hang out with my
boys and train and do my thing.
>> Um, there's an NFL academy in Australia.
>> No, I didn't know about it, so I guess
No, I guess I don't. But maybe I should.
>> Yeah, I definitely will. I didn't I
didn't know they were doing that. I'm
I'm more focused on my uh my punting
crew back home. So, I definitely need to
check out the other positions and
themies back home. That'd be cool.
>> Thanks, Mike.
Congratulations.
>> Thank you, guys. Appreciate